{
  "2": [
    { "prompt": "ես", "answer": "եմ" },
    { "prompt": "դու", "answer": "ես" },
    { "prompt": "նա", "answer": "է" },
    { "prompt": "եմ", "answer": "ես" },
    { "prompt": "ես", "answer": "դու" },
    { "prompt": "է", "answer": "նա" }
  ],
  "3": [
    { "prompt": "ես", "answer": "ունեմ" },
    { "prompt": "դու", "answer": "ունես" },
    { "prompt": "նա", "answer": "ունի" },
    { "prompt": "ունեմ", "answer": "ես" },
    { "prompt": "ունես", "answer": "դու" },
    { "prompt": "ունի", "answer": "նա" }
  ]
}
